Katherine Armitage

Seattle, WA | kmarmitage@gmail.com | github.com/karmitage | linkedin.com/in/katherinearmitage

Profile

I'm a creative problem-solver with experience in back-end and front-end development. In my work as a business analyst, I create ETL processes & reporting in a Hadoop ecosystem - automating manual tasks, optimizing existing processes, and collaborating with technical and non-technical stakeholders. I'm currently enrolled in a full stack web development course at the University of Washington with the intention of transitioning to full time software development.

Technical Skills

Proficient Familiar

Javascript, HTML, CSS, jQuery, SQL, Hive, Git Python, Spark, Jupyter Notebooks, Node.js

Experience

Getty Images: Seattle, WA

Senior Business Analyst, Feb 2019 - present

I create ETL processes, optimize existing jobs, & develop table/dmart architecture for a variety of internal reporting suites. I work closely with developers on our internal data services team, and have played a key role in transitioning jobs from a MS SQL environment to a Hive ecosystem.

Marketing Analyst, May 2016 - Feb 2019

I built, tested & maintained new reporting for email marketing and web analytics teams, from data architecture/etl to front-end presentation. I was the first person on my broader team to build jobs in Hive, and the first to adopt Git.

Marketing Specialist, May 2015 - May 2016

I worked closely with analytics & sales stakeholders to develop and implement a predictive lead scoring model, increasing qualified leads by 30%. I also analyzed digital marketing spend performance across all geos, identifying growth areas for further investment.

Marketing Specialist (contractor), Feb 2014 - May 2015

I was the point-person for the Marketing budget. I worked closely with finance & marketing leadership to forecast & analyze spend for all cost centers/geos, including digital marketing.

Additional Experience:

Executive Assistant, Exvere: Sep 2012 - Feb 2014

Associate Senior Living Advisor, A Place for Mom: Jun 2011 - Sep 2012

Writing & ESL tutor, Tacoma Community College: Jan - Nov 2010

Education

University of Washington Coding Bootcamp: Mar - Sep 2019 (expected)

Full stack web development course focused on Javascript

North Seattle Community College: 2013-2014

Foundational computer science coursework (Python & Java)

St. John's College: 2005-2009

Bachelor of Arts, Philosophy & History of Math & Science